【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧
唉 我真想念茱莉
Man, I sure miss Julie.
西班牙侏儒
Spanish midgets.
西班牙侏儒摔跤
Spanish midgets wrestling.
茱莉 好 是的 我懂你为何会这样联想
Julie. Okay. Yes, I see how you got there.
你有想过那玩意儿是用来做什么的吗
You ever figure out what that thing's for?
是这样的 我在试着过滤电话
No, see, I'm trying this new screening thing.
我认为 如果我老是接电话
You know,  I figure if I'm always answering the phone,
人们会觉得我没有生活
people will think I don't have a life.
我的天 罗德里格从来不会被压制
My God. Rodrigo never gets pinned.
哔声要来了 你知道该怎么做
Here comes the beep. You know what to do.
你好 我要找鲍勃
Hello. I'm looking for Bob.
我是洁德
This is Jade.
我不知道你是否还在用这个号码
I don't know if you're still at this number,
我只是想起 以前我们在一起的美好时光
but I was just thinking about us and how great it was.
我知道那已是三年前的事了
And, well, I know it's been three years.
但我希望我们能够重修旧好
But I was kind of hoping we could hook up again.
你知道吗 我几乎没勇气打这个电话
You know, I barely had the nerve to make this call.
所以你知道我做了什么吗      什么
so, you know what I did?         What?
我喝得微醺 而且一丝不挂
I got a little drunk and naked.
我是鲍勃
Bob here.
《老友记》蓝光版 第02季 第05集
五块牛排和一条茄子 Five Steaks and an Eggplant
调校制作：海盗美剧 寒 枫
字幕编辑：海盗美剧 小龟快快跑
那么 你近来怎么样
So, what have you been up to?
你知道的 跟平常一样
Oh, you know the usual.
教有氧运动
Teaching aerobics,
玩得太过火
partying way too much.
如果你想知道的话
Oh, and in case you were wondering,
新的007电影海报上的那双腿 是我的
those are my legs on the new James Bond poster.
你能等一下吗 我有另一通电话
Can you hold on a moment? I have another call.
我爱她      我懂
I love her.         I know.
我回来了      我们要不要见个面
I'm back.        So are we gonna get together or what?
当然要
Absolutely.
明天下午怎么样
How about tomorrow afternoon?
你知道格林威治村的中央公园咖啡馆吗 五点?
Do you know, Central Perk in the village? Say fiveish?
太好了 到时见      好
Great. I'll see you then.         Okay.
很好
Okay.
装个电话终于物有所值了
Having a phone has finally paid off.
就算你模仿鲍勃很像
Even though you do do a good Bob impression.
我想 她明天见到你的时候
I'm thinking when she sees you tomorrow,
大概还是会发现 嘿 你不是鲍勃
she's probably gonna realize, hey, you're not Bob.
我所希望的是 当鲍勃没出现时
I am hoping that when Bob doesn't show up,
她会向邻桌的陌生人张开的双臂间  寻求慰藉
she will seek comfort in the open arms of the wry stranger at the next table.
我的天 你邪恶到了极点
Oh my God. You are pure evil.
好吧 邪恶到极点
Okay, pure evil,
饥渴又孤单
horny and alone.
这个我试过了
I've done this.
对 大家都在
Yeah, yeah, everybody's here.
嘿 各位 向在新墨西哥的茱莉说声嗨
Hey, everybody, say hi to Julie in New Mexico.
嗨 茱莉
Hi Julie.
好 趁着罗斯在讲电话
Okay. While Ross is on the phone,
他生日 每人交62块给我
everybody owes me 62 bucks for his birthday.
有没有可能 你取个整数就好
Is there any chance that you're rounding up from
像是20块
you know, like from, like 20?
拜托 我们要买礼物 看演唱会和买蛋糕
Hey, come on, we got the gift, the concert and the cake.
我们需要蛋糕吗
Do we need a cake?
听着 我知道金额有点高
Look guys, I know it's a little steep.
没错 嗖
Yeah! Whoosh!
不过 是罗斯的生日
But it's Ross.
对 是为了罗斯      你说得对
Yeah, it's Ross.         Yeah, you're right.
好了 大家待会见 我得走了
All right? Okay. I'll see you later. I gotta go.
去做一件事
Do a thing.
好 亲爱的 我晚点儿再打给你
Okay, sweetheart, I'll call you later tonight.
等等 嘿 嘿 嘿
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hey, hey, hey.
你不会真要这么做吧
You're not really gonna go through with this, are you?
我想我也许就会
You know I think I might just.
那么 你们今晚的晚餐要怎么办
So, what are you guys doing for dinner tonight?
我想 我必须开始 为罗斯的生日存钱
Well, I guess I gotta start saving up for Ross's birthday.
所以我想 我待在家里 喝西北风就好了
So I guess, I'll just stay home and eat dust bunnies.
你们能相信 要花那么多钱吗
Can you believe how much this is gonna cost?
你们有没有过这种感觉
Do you guys ever get the feeling that,
钱德他们几个 不了解
Chandler and those guys just don't get that,
我们赚的钱不如他们多
we don't make as much money as they do?
对 没错      真的
Yes.Yeah         Really?
他们老是说 咱们去这里 咱们去那里
It's like they're always saying, "Let's go here, let's go there."
像是我们负担得起 去这里去那里一样
Like we can afford to go here and there.
对 而且我们总是必须去 某个不错的地方
Yes, yes, and it's, and we always have to go to, you know, someplace nice.
我知道      对吧
I know.        You know?
老天 像是我们没什么说话的余地
God! It's not like we can say anything about it,
因为 像这是为了生日
because, like, this is a birthday thing, you know?
而且是为了罗斯
And it's for Ross.
为了罗斯      为了罗斯
For Ross.         For Ross.
我的天啊
Oh my God!
嗨      怎么了
Hi.         What?
是这样的 我在工作
Okay. I'm at work
只是平凡的一天 你们知道的 切切炒炒
just an ordinary day, you know, chop chop chop saute saute saute.
突然 经理里昂叫我到他办公室
All of a sudden, Leon, the manager calls me into his office.
原来他们开除了午餐主厨
Turns out they fired the head lunch chef.
猜猜谁得到了那份工作
And guess who got the job?
如果不是你 这故事还真悲惨
If it's not you, this is a horrible story.
幸好是我      噢
Fortunately, it is me.         Oh!
而且他们升我为采购主管 多谢大家
And they made me head of purchasing. Thank you very much.
真棒
That's so cool.
我刚刚在楼下碰到钱德和罗斯
Anyway, I just ran into Chandler and Ross downstairs.
我想我们应该出去庆祝一下
I think we should go out and celebrate.
找个不错的地方
You know, someplace nice.
不错的地方      对
Someplace nice.         Yeah.
你们认为 我的肾能卖多少钱
How much you think I can get for my kidney?
我告诉你 你不能这么做
I'm telling you, you can't do this.
拜托 我用普通方法绝对追不到那种女生
Oh, come on, I can't never get a girl like that with conventional methods.
那不是重点
That doesn't matter.
她本来是打电话给鲍勃的
She wanted to call Bob.
我们知道 鲍勃才应该跟她在一起
Hey, for all we know, Bob is who she was meant to be with.
你也许在破坏 两个人追求快乐的机会
You may be destroying two people's chance for happiness.
我们不认识鲍勃
We don't know Bob.
好吗 我们认识我 我们喜欢我 拜托让我快乐
Okay? We know me. We like me. Please let me be happy.
过去那里 告诉那女人真相
Go over there and tell that woman the truth.
好吧
All right.
去
Go.
嗨
Hi.
听着 我必须
Listen, I have to,
我必须坦承一件事
I have to confess something.
什么事
Yes?
放你鸽子的那个人是烂人
Whoever stood you up is a jerk.
你怎么      我不知道
How did you?        I don't know.
我只是有这种奇怪的感应
I just had this weird sense. You know?
不过这就是我 我古怪而敏感
But that's me. I'm weird and sensitive.
要纸巾吗
Tissue?
谢谢
Thanks.
不 你留着吧
No, no, you keep the pack.
我今天已经哭过了
I'm all cried out today.
好了 好了
Okay, okay.
现在来敬我的妹妹 新上任的午餐主厨
Here is to my sister the newly appointed head lunch chef...
而且还负责采购
Who is also in charge of purchasing.
新上任的午餐主厨 还负责采购
Newly appointed head lunch chef, who is also in charge of purchasing...
罗兰不在的时候 还有自己的小办公桌
Who has her own little desk when Roland's not there.
午餐主厨 采购 罗兰不在时有自己的小办公桌
Lunch chef, purchasing, own little desk when Roland's not there...
敬我的妹妹
Here's to my little sister...
等等 我还有一个寻呼机
Oh, wait, and I got a beeper.
好酷
Oh, cool！
没关系 我先等等      对不起
That's fine.I'll just wait.         Aw, sorry.
对不起
Oh, sorry, sorry.
敬摩妮卡
Monica.
大家准备点菜了吗
Are we ready to order?
我们还没看菜单
Oh. You know what, we haven't even looked yet.
那你们看过之后再叫我
Well, when you do, just let me know.
我就在我的座位边上引颈期盼
I'll be right over there on the edge of my seat.
哇 看看这些价格
Wow, look at these prices.
是啊 真不得了
Yeah, these are pretty "cha-ching."
对啊 这些是什么 名牌鸡吗
I know. What are these, famous chickens?
抱歉 我迟到了 摩妮卡 恭喜      谢了
Sorry.I'm late. Congratulations, Mon.         Thanks.
我不为迟到感到抱歉
I'm not sorry. I'm late.
我跟洁德一起的下午 相当不可思议
How incredible was my afternoon with Jade?
根据她在我的答录机上给你留的言 的确不可思议
Well, pretty incredible, according to the message she left you on my machine.
嘿 钱德 为什么这个女人
Hey, Chandler, why is this woman
会在我的答录机上给你留言
leaving a message for you on my machine?
我必须告诉她 我的号码是你的号码
See, I had to tell her that my number was your number.
因为我不能告诉她 我的号码是我的号码
Because I couldn't tell her my number was my number.
因为她以为 我的号码是鲍勃的号码
Because she thinks my number is Bob's number.
再告诉我一次 罗普先生打来时 我该怎么做
Hey, tell me again. What do I do when Mr. Roper calls?
我能斗胆问一下吗
Do I dare ask?
好 我先来一份生牛肉
Yes, I'll start with the carpaccio.
再来一份烤明虾
And then I'll have the grilled prawns.
听起来不错 我也一样
That sounds great, same for me.
这位男士呢
And for the gentleman?
我要泰式鸡肉披萨
Yeah,I'll have the Thai chicken pizza.
但是 假如我不要坚果 韭葱等材料
But, hey, look, if I get it without the nuts and leeks and stuff,
会便宜一点吗
is it cheaper?
你以为会 是不是
You'd think, wouldn't you?
小姐      好的
Miss?         Okay.
我要配餐沙拉
I will have the side salad.
它要配什么餐呢
And what would that be on the side of?
我不知道
I don't know.
不如就把它放在我的水旁边好了
Why don't you just put it right here next to my water?
那么你呢
And for you?
我要一碗黄瓜汤
I'm gonna have a cup of the cucumber soup.
以及
and,
保重
take care.
我要一份卡津鲶鱼      还要别的吗
I will have the Cajun catfish.         Anything else?
要 来一段《情歌销魂》怎样
Yes, how about a verse of "Killing Me Softly"?
你会朝我的鱼打喷嚏 是不是
You're gonna sneeze on my fish, aren't you?
加上小费 除以6
Plus tip, divided by six,
好 每个人28块      好的
Okay, everyone owes 28 bucks.        Okay!
每个人吗
Everyone?
你说得对 真抱歉
Oh, you're right. I'm sorry.
谢谢
Thank you.
今晚是摩妮卡的大日子 她不该付钱
It's Monica's big night. She shouldn't pay.
谢谢
Aw, thank you.
所以我们五个人
So five of us is
各付33.5块
$33.50 a piece.
不 才不要 抱歉 不可能
No. No way. Sorry, not gonna happen.
等等 毕业舞会情景重现
Whoa. Whoa. Prom night flashback.
抱歉 摩妮卡 你升职 我真的很高兴
Sorry, Monica. I'm really happy you got promoted.
但是冷黄瓜糊要三十几块
But cold cucumber mush for 30something bucks?
不
No.
瑞秋只吃了一小份沙拉
Rachel just had that little salad.
乔伊吃了一小块披萨
And Joey with his, like, teeny pizza.
好了 菲比
Okay, Pheebs.
不如我们各付各的 好吗
How about we'll each just pay for what we had, okay?
没什么大不了      对你是这样
It's no big deal.         Not for you.
好了 怎么回事
All right, what's going on?
好吧 听着 我现在真的不想提这个
Okay, look you guys, I really don't wanna get into this right now.
这只会让大家都不舒服
I think it'll just make everybody uncomfortable.
好 没关系 好
Oh, fine. All right, fine.
干嘛      你们可以告诉我们
What? Whoa, whoa.         You can tell us.
对 拜托 是我们 好吗 我们能接受
Yeah hello? It's us. All right? We'll be fine.
是啊
Yeah!
好吧
Okay.
我们三个觉得
We three feel like that,
有时候你们不了解
sometimes you guys don't get that,
我们没你们那么有钱
we don't have as much money as you.
好      我听到了
Okay         I hear you.
我们可以讨论一下这件事
We can talk about that.
那么
Well, then
就来吧
let's.
我猜 我只是从没想到 钱会构成问题
Well, I guess I just never think of money as an issue.
因为你有钱      这一点说得好
That's because you have it.         That's a good point.
那么 为什么你们以前从没提过这件事
So, how come you guys haven't talked about this before?
因为总是有特别的事情
Because it's always something, you know?
像是摩妮卡的新职位
Like with Monica's new job,
或是罗斯生日要盛大庆祝
or the whole Ross birthday hoopla.
什么 等等 嘿
What? Whoa, hey.
我可不希望我的生日 造成任何的不愉快
I don't want my birthday to be the source of any kind of negative.
到时候会有盛大的庆祝吗
There's gonna be a hoopla?
基本上 有一件事
Basically there's the thing,
然后还有那件事之后的事
and then the stuff after the thing and it's...
如果可以让大家好过些 我们可以忘了那件事
If it makes anybody feel better, then we can just forget the thing.
只送礼物就好
And we'll just do the gift.
礼物 那件事不是礼物
Gift? The thing's not the gift?
不 那件事就是 我们要去看"混混与自大狂"演唱会
No, the thing was we were gonna go see "Hootie and the Blowfish".
混混与 我的天
Hootie and the...Oh my...
我听广播就好了
I can catch them on the radio.
不 我现在觉得内疚了 你想去听演唱会的
No. Now I feel bad. You wanna go to the concert.
不 听着 这是我生日
No, look, hey, it's my birthday.
最重要的是我们大家能在一起
And the important thing is that we all be together.
我们所有人      在一起
All of us.         Together.
不是在演唱会场
Not at the concert.
好吧 谢谢      好吧
Okay. Thank you.         Yeah.
谢谢      好吧
Thanks!        Yeah!
那个伊波拉病毒 真要命吧
So, the Ebola virus, that's gotta suck, huh?
天呀 摩妮卡 袋子里有什么
Gee Monica. What's in the bag?
我不知道 钱德 咱们来看看
I don't know, Chandler. Let's take a look.
像是短剧表演
Oh, it's like a skit.
原来是六人晚餐 五块牛排
Why, it's dinner for six. Five steaks,
和给菲比的一条茄子
and an eggplant for Phoebe.
我们餐厅换了肉类供应商
We switched meat suppliers at work.
新供应商给了我这些牛排 算是谢礼
And the new guys gave me the steaks as sort of a thankyou.
等等 还有 钱德 那信封里有什么
But wait, there's more. Hey Chandler, what is in that envelope?
对了 刚在走廊练习时 好像没这么呆
By the way, this didn't seem so dorky out in the hall.
快点
Come on.
原来是 "混混与自大狂"的六张门票
Why, it's six tickets to "Hootie and the Blowfish".
自大狂
The Blowfish.
我们付钱的 所以别担心 由我们请客
It's on us, all right? So don't worry. This is our treat.
那么 谢谢
So, thank you.
你们能更冷淡一点吗
Could you be less enthused?
听着 这是很好的表示 真的
Look, it's a nice gesture. It is.
可是感觉像是
But it just feels like...
像
Like?
施舍      施舍
Charity.         Charity?
我们只是想表达一番好意
We're just trying to do a nice thing here.
没错 罗斯 你得了解
Yeah, Ross, you have to understand,
你的好意 令我们觉得 我们是这么渺小
your nice thing makes us feel about this big.
其实是 令我们觉得这么渺小
Actually, it makes us feel that big.
什么 我搞不明白
What? I don't understand.
我们好像怎么做 你们都觉得不对
I mean, it's like we can't win with you guys.
没错 如果你们觉得渺小 也许那不是我们的错
Yeah, I mean, if you guys feel this big, maybe that's not our fault.
也许那只是你们的感受
Maybe that's just how you feel.
噢
Oh!
现在 你在断定我们的感受
Now you're telling us how we feel.
各位 看见了吧 我们真不该提起这件事的
You guys, see? Okey! We never should have talked about this.
好吧 我不去演唱会了
All right, I'm gonna pass on the concert.
因为我现在实在是没那个心情去"混”
Because I'm just not in a very Hootie place right now.
我也一样      我也是
Me neither.         Me too.
各位 我们都已经买好票了
Guys, we bought the tickets.
刚好你们有空座位 可以放你们的皇冠什么的
Oh well, then you'll have extra seats, you know, for all your tiaras and stuff.
你说话时 为什么看着我
Why did you look at me when you said that?
这下我猜 我们都不能去了
So I guess now we can't go.
什么 拜托 你们想做什么就去做
What? Come on, you do what you want.
我们非得做什么都在一起吗
Do we always have to do everything together?
知道吗 你说得对
You know what? You're right.
好      好
Fine.         Fine.
好      好的
Fine.         All right.
我们要去了
We're gonna go.
还有六小时才开始 我们到时候再去
It's not for another six hours. We're gonna go then.
钱德      有
Chandler?         Yeah.
天啊
Oh, jeez.
你准备好没      好了 好了
Are you ready?         Yes. Yes.
让我拿上西装外套 跟你说我今天跟人上床了
Just let me grab my jacket and tell you I had sex today.
什么 你今天跟人上床了
What? You had sex today?
从别人嘴里说出来 听起来更酷
Wow! It sounds even cooler when somebody else says it.
我简直是棒呆了
I was awesome, okay?
她拼命咬着嘴唇 才不会尖叫出来
She was biting her lip to stop from screaming.
哇喔
Wow!
我知道我有阵子没做了 但我把那当成好的迹象
Now, I know it's been a while, but I took that as a good sign.
还在过滤电话
Still doing the screening thing?
我今天跟人上床了
I had sex today.
我再也不用去接那个电话了
I never have to answer that phone again.
哔声要来了 你知道该怎么做
Here comes the beep. You know what to do.
嘿 鲍勃 是我洁德 听着
He Bob.It's Jade. Listen.
我只想告诉你 你那天放我鸽子
I just wanted to tell you that I was really hurt,
我非常难过
when you didn't show up the other day.
后来 我认识了一个男的
And just so you know, I ended up meeting a guy.
我是鲍勃
Bob here.
喔 嗨
Oh, hi.
你认识了别人吗
So, you met someone, huh?
是的 我认识了别人
Yes. Yes, I did.
事实上 我两小时前跟他上床了
In fact, I had sex with him two hours ago.
那么 他表现怎样
So, how was he?
鲍勃 他根本比不上你
Oh Bob, he was nothing compared to you.
我必须咬着嘴唇 才不会叫出你的名字
I had to bite my lip to keep from screaming your name.
那令我很欣慰
Well, that makes me feel so good.
过程很笨拙又颠簸
It was just so awkward and bumpy.
颠簸
Bumpy?
也许他有某种很酷的新风格
Maybe he had some kind of new cool style,
只是你不熟悉
that you're not familiar with.
也许你只要习惯就好
And, maybe you have to get used to it.
根本没多少时间可以让我习惯
Well, there really wasn't much time to get used to it.
你懂我意思吧
You know what I mean?
你知道吗 我实在没心情听这个
You know what? I'm not gonna be able to enjoy this.
是 我懂 这是我生日 我们应该全部在一起
Yeah I know. It's my birthday. We all should be here.
那么走吧
So let's go.
也许我们该留下来听一首歌
Well, you know, maybe we should stay for one song.
对 假如我们现在离开 对他们很没礼貌
Yeah. I mean, it would be rude to them for us to leave now.
说不定 他们现在正玩得很开心呢
You know, the guys are probably having a great time.
拜托 两位 再来一次
Come on, you guys. One more time.
好吧
Okay.
一      不是
One.         No.
非常精彩
That was amazing.
太棒了 非常棒
Excellent.That was excellent.
我不敢相信 他们错过这个
I can't believe the guys missed this.
什么人 喔 对了
What guys? Oh, yeah.
打扰一下 你是摩妮卡盖勒吗
Excuse me. You're Monica Geller, aren't you?
我认识你吗      你以前是我的保姆
Do I know you?         You used to be my babysitter.
我的天 小史提夫费雪
Oh, my God. Little Stevie Fisher?
你近来好吗
How have you been?
很好 我现在是个律师
Good, good. I'm a lawyer now.
你不可能是律师 你才八岁
You can't be a lawyer.You're 8.
很高兴见到你 我得回后台了
Well, listen, it was nice to see you. I gotta run backstage.
等等 后台
Wait, backstage?
对 我的事务所代表这乐团
Oh, yeah. My firm represents the band.
罗斯      钱德
Ross.         Chandler.
你们想去认识一下他们吗
Look, you guys wanna meet the group?
当然 我们想
Yeah, we do.
来吧
Come on.
你以前也跟我老爸乱搞过吗
So, look, are you one of the ones that fooled around with my dad?
你们好      生日快乐
Hey, you guys.        Happy birthday.
谢谢 谢谢
Oh, thank you. Thanks.
所以
So,
你们昨晚过得怎样
How was your night last night?
蛮逊的 你们呢
Oh well, it pretty much sucked. How was yours?
我们的也很逊
Yeah, ours pretty much sucked too.
但是我碰到了史提夫费雪
Oh, but I did run into Stevie Fisher.
你记得他吗
Do you remember him?
当然 我以前当过他的保姆
Oh, yeah. I used to babysit him.
他爸还好吗
Hey, how's his dad?
很好
Good.
除此之外 整个晚上实在没什么好提的
Aside from that, the whole evening was pretty much a bust.
对 我们很想你们
Yeah, we really missed you guys.
听着 我们想说 整件事实在是太傻了
Yeah, look, we were just saying, this whole thing is so stupid.
我们必须真的真的 不让钱这种事情影响到
We just have to really really really not let stuff like this, money get like...
那是吻痕吗
Is that a hickey?
不 我只是
Oh, no, I just...
我跌倒了
I fell down.
倒在别人嘴唇上
On someone's lips?
你的吻痕是从哪来的
Where'd you get the hickey?
大概是派对      什么派对
You know, a party or...        What party?
其实不太算派对 只是一群人聚在一起
Well, it wasn't a party, so much as a gathering of people.
有食物和音乐以及
With food and music and...
以及乐团
and the band.
你们跟"混混与自大狂" 一起"混"
You partied with Hootie and the Blowfish?
没错 显然史提夫跟"混混"很熟
Yes. Apparently, Stevie and "Hootie" are like this.
那吻痕是谁给你的
Who gave you that hickey?
应该是一个"自大狂"的杰作
That would be the work of a "Blowfish".
我不敢相信 我不敢相信
I can't believe it. I can't believe this.
我们只是呆坐在家
We're just like sitting at home,
试着猜乔伊比几根手指
just trying to guess Joey's fingers,
你们则在外面 寻欢作乐
and you guys are out, like, partying and having fun.
以及 "嘿 自大狂 来吸我的脖子"
And you know, all, "Hey, Blowfish, suck on my neck."
听着 别怪我们 你们原本也可以去的
Hey, look, don't blame us. You guys could've been there, you know?
干嘛 参与你的 "穷朋友施舍计划"
Oh what? As part of your "Poor Friends Outreach" program?
太好了 公司打来的
Oh, great. It's work.
我不知道该说什么
Look,  I don't know what to say.
很遗憾我们赚得比你们多
I'm sorry that we make more than you.
但我们不打算觉得愧疚
But we're not gonna feel guilty about it.
我们是辛苦工作得到的
We work really hard for it.
那我们没辛苦工作吗
And we don't work hard?
我是摩妮卡 刚有人呼我
Yeah. hi, it's Monica. I just got a page.
我只是说 有时我们想做一些比较花钱的事
I'm just saying that sometimes we like to do stuff that costs a little more.
你觉得我们成了你的绊脚石      对
Oh, and you feel like we hold you back.         Yes.
噢      不对
Oh!        No.
里昂 等一下 大家安静
Leon, Leon, wait. Shh! Guys.
等等 我不了解
Wait. I don't understand.
那些牛排只是供应商的礼物
Those steaks were just a gift from the meat vendor.
那不是回扣
That was not a kickback.
拜托 我会补回去 我们就此忘掉这件事
I mean, come on, I'll just replace them and we can forget the whole thing.
什么企业政策
What corporate policy?
不 是
No...Yeah.
好的
Okay.
我刚刚被开除了
I just got fired.
这是你的帐单 4.12元
Here's your check. That'll be four twelve.
我来付
Let me get that.
你有五块吗
You got 5 bucks?
哔声要来了 你知道该怎么做
Here comes the beep. You know what to do.
嗨 是我
Hi,it's me.
听着 鲍勃 或许我不该这么做
Listen, Bob, I'm probably way out of line here.
毕竟已经过去三年了
I mean, it has been three years.
你可能正在跟别人交往
And you're probably seeing someone else now.
但是假如我们能共度一晚
But if we could just have one night together,
就当看在往日的情份上
just for old time's sake,
共度火辣 热情 狂野的一晚
one hot, steamy, wild night.
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧